[♪ opening theme song playing]
[DERA]
I'm so drinkin' on his tab.
Hm?
Well...
[Dera smirks]
We're already here,
in the middle of the city.
Might as well have some fun!
Time for a lesson.
[YURU AND RIGHT] Uh?
[DERA] You're gonna learn
about the world!
[Right yells]
[Yuru exclaiming]
[Yuru laughs]
[Right exclaiming]
[Yuru exclaiming]
[Right cheering]
[MAN] Uh?
[crowd cheering]
[Dera cheering]
Pick up the pace!
[Dera groans softly]
[YURU] The horses down here
are huge, and so fast!
Riding them must take practice.
Really liked the one
that finished in first place.
I wonder how much it would cost.
Please, no.
Hana would divorce me.
But if you want
something reasonable,
let me know.
Horses, cattle.
Forget the livestock.
[YURU] Besides that, the thing
I need most would be arrows.
I've only got
a bow at your place.
Nothing to fire.
Yeah, that's tricky.
Where do they sell arrows?
I could craft my own,
if I had the materials.
[DERA] Uh? Hmm.
[Yuru and Right exclaiming]
You mean
all of this is for sale?
Yup.
[DERA] What do you need
to make arrows?
[YURU] Some bamboo,
thread, and a knife.
And something hard
for the arrowheads.
[DERA] What about fletching?
[YURU] We've got
the feathers from the pheasant
I sold you the other day.
Think we can get an entire deer?
What?
I can boil the skin and organs
to fix myself up some glue.
And how would that smell?
We'd get complaints
from our neighbors.
-Use this.
-[YURU] Uh?
-[DERA] Introducing, wood glue!
-[YURU] What does that mean?
[DERA] Here, check it out.
[YURU] That's so convenient!
[CLERK] Next customer!
They really have
everything down here.
[clerk stammers]
A one. A two. A three.
Thank you, have a nice day.
Hey, boss.
I seem to be hallucinating.
Can I have a break?
What? Quit screwing around
and get back to work.
[CLERK] I hate this job!
That's peculiar.
Seems the lass with
the beeping device could see us.
If she were a Daemon Wielder,
we would smell them on her.
It's like you said before.
Some people just have the sight.
It can also happen when
someone's badly sleep-deprived.
We should get you
some clothes, too.
[Yuru gasps]
A scarecrow?
Huh.
I like that
the clothes down here
have many storage compartments.
Yep! Grab what you like!
I prefer wearing black.
It makes bloodstains easier
to hide.
[DERA] Oh, good, he's basing
his fashion choices
on blood splatter!
-Need some boxers?
-[YURU] Some what?
[DERA] A kind of underpants.
They're like loincloths.
[YURU]
I'll stick with what I know.
I don't like these.
[Dera chuckles softly]
Excuse me.
Do you have loincloths?
I'm afraid not. Only those.
-Oh... That's right.
-[DERA] Hm?
This reminded me
of when I would go hunting.
At times, bandits would attack
when I was by myself.
And just like
my father taught me,
if I thought
they wanted to kill me,
I'd kill first in response.
Even after I buried them
or sent them downstream,
something always felt off.
Now, I can finally say
what that was.
These bandits weren't young,
but their hands were so clean.
Where I come from,
the labor means
you're gonna get dirty.
And past a certain age,
the dirt really settles in.
So nails and knuckles
can't be washed clean.
They were like you.
Their hands were
in good condition
because they lived
in a place that allowed it.
But now I see why.
And why they were wearing
these boxer things.
Did you strip them?
The bandits came up there
to kill me.
Someone sent them
to the mountain as assassins.
They would've lost your trust
if you came back
after a villager
you knew took your life.
This way, you'd believe
you gained the power of Seal
after an outsider cut you down.
Their hold on you
would be all the stronger.
We don't know for certain
that it was the village
who sent them.
But I can't trust them
anymore, either.
What if something happened
in the mountains
while you were by yourself,
huh?
Even though I want to.
The barrier to Higashi Village
is not an easy code to crack.
There's only a few besides me
who could.
How nice.
That narrows it down.
Shall we lay a trap for them?
[YURU] Yeah.
Better to take the initiative.
I thought you might say that.
[YURU] The winner
of the hunt is the one
with the best positioning.
-Speaking of which, Dera...
-Yeah?
We're being followed.
I know. I count three.
[YURU] One, two, three.
And they're taking turns
tailing us.
Think they're Kagemori guys?
Man, they're pieces of work.
Don't look behind you.
Understood. Uh, hold on.
You told me you didn't want them
to find you,
but you were in that painting?
The thing Asa's device made.
Wouldn't they be able
to use that to identify you?
[DERA] Eh, too late.
Rich people can shell out
for security cameras
all over their mansions.
[YURU] Shell out?
I knew when I arrived,
they'd have my face.
Had to write that off
as the cost for picking you up.
[ASA] The two of us.
[Asa laughs]
Hmm.
[ASA] Now where's that
photo editing app?
There.
Asa, did you get
a picture of Tadera?
We'd like to see it.
He wasn't in the frame.
He's potentially dangerous.
Your information will help.
Wait. He's not?
Afraid not.
He wasn't in the one you took
of your brother?
Afraid not.
Haruo,
check the security camera.
We'll take anything
we've got on him.
And if you find any footage
of my brother, I'll take it!
[Jin sighs]
[HAMURA] I mentioned
the bearded guy
in the camo jacket.
Name's Akishima.
And he's the one you go to
for work on the down low.
Contacted us same as usual
for a job with pay
through the roof.
[TACHIKAWA]
This is my call history.
He reached out yesterday
at midnight to explain
what this gig would entail.
Timing lines up perfectly
on my phone, too.
[GONZO] Hmm.
[TACHIKAWA] I figure he must've
just called everyone in the area
who could get there fast.
[HAMURA]
It's like I told you before.
None of us on the team
met each other
till we got there.
[HARUO] Midnight, huh?
Exactly when we finished up
our fight with Yuru
and were driving back
to the manor.
I'm checking my own logs,
and it seems like that's
when Jin called me, too.
About what time did you actually
enter the manor?
It was definitely after 1:30,
but before 2:00 a.m.
[SAKURAZAWA]
Right when you came to me
-to get your leg treated.
-[JIN] Seems so.
[GONZO] We have this manor
surrounded by a barrier.
At that time of night,
the only ones who should be
able to enter
are members of the family
and those they invite in.
If there was a Kagemori
at the gate who invited you in,
we'd like to know who,
so we can prevent
future internal transgressions.
Beardy... Akishima was
the only person we saw.
Actually, the west gate
was open,
and we walked in
with no problem.
Yeah, good point.
We were told the manor
was full of daemons,
so we just needed to get inside.
After that,
blending in was no problem.
Hold on there.
Which gate did you say again?
What? The west gate.
The west side of the manor
doesn't have a gate
you could've gone through.
Huh?
No? It does!
You're wrong.
The entire west side is a wall.
There's no place
you could've entered.
Much less
without drawing attention.
[both gasp]
Fuyuki.
Sir.
[gasping]
Stop! What are you gonna do
to my partners?
Chill out, dude.
Fuyuki isn't going to kill 'em.
This pair is known
as Kori-Henge.
Their master gave them
personal names.
This is Akai and Midori.
Their current master
is Makoto Tachikawa.
She was born on May 4th,
in the year 1997.
She's a dropout
at Ariake Women's U.
She resides in Shinkiba,
Koto-ku, Tokyo.
She has one sister
and has one brother.
Parents...
Divorced in August, 2008.
Her mother won
full custody of her,
though she is now
in the hospital.
Subject is currently unemployed.
-She accepted this job...
-Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-...to help pay for her--
-Ah, pardon me.
It doesn't seem right of me
to expose a lady's
personal information like that.
Wrong for a guy, too.
Whisper, could you
cease speaking for a moment?
As you wish.
[FUYUKI] Hmm.
-[Tachikawa whimpers]
-[FUYUKI] Ah, yes, good.
What the hell was that?
The next one please, embrace.
[Daifuku and Ohagi grunting]
[ASA]
Please be gentle with them.
I am never anything but gentle.
Pair name, Yin-Yang.
No personal names.
Their current master is Asa.
Their previous master
is Kenichi Hamura.
He was born on the 16th of June,
in the year 1992.
-[trembling]
-[FUYUKI] Current residence...
Yes. Got it.
I see. Debt from your gambling.
Both of them told us the truth.
They really did meet
on site for this job.
Who is this dude trampling
all over Japan's privacy laws?
[FUYUKI] Fuyuki Kuroya.
As for my daemon pair,
you may call them Blacklist.
They can extract information
on a daemon's master,
past or present.
And one touch is all it takes.
Now that we know
you really are just mercs
and there's no lingering
affiliations to worry about...
if you're struggling for money,
you can have a job, with us!
[BOTH] Huh?
Well, I don't wanna sound like
I don't appreciate
your kindness.
But you're not gonna kill us?
I'll just work you until
you wish you were dead!
[both whimper]
[GONZO]
Your mother's hospital bills...
Are they expensive?
Oh, um... Yes, very...
I'll front you the cost
of everything.
Tell your mother to rest easy
and to devote herself
to feeling better.
[TACHIKAWA]
Thank you so much, sir!
Any chance you could
front me some... [grunts]
You can work off your debts
the slow and steady way!
To start, the manor is
an absolute mess! Clean it!
[TACHIKAWA AND HAMURA]
Oh! Yes, sir!
[NATSUKI] Are you sure
they're safe to leave alive?
[GONZO] It's fine.
We know who they are
and where they live,
among other details.
And it never hurts to have
some more cannon fodder
on our staff.
Of course, sir.
And what should we do
with the other Daemon Wielders
we captured?
For the ones whose daemons
died in the battle,
force them into contracts
with new ones later.
After that, use Blacklist
to get their information.
If you do figure out
who the mastermind is,
round them up with everyone
they're associated with
and kill them.
[NATSUKI] We're on it, sir.
-[birds chirping]
-[sweeping]
[HAMURA] Excuse me, miss.
Is there any chance you could
give me those daemons back?
I will consider it.
Did you name them yet?
Oh, uh...
Daifuku. Ohagi.
What?
-[Gabby and Asa laugh]
-[ASA] Like the snacks?
Oh, that's adorable!
What's the big deal?
I like sweets, okay?
Wouldn't expect
such peaceful names from a guy
who acts as tough as you do.
[HAMURA] Give me a break!
Says the guy
who named his daemons
after the words
for love and sincerity.
Like those teeth of yours
have some awesome name?
Of course!
One is Joe William
Frederic Gabriel the First,
and the other one is
Kirk Douglas Auldglaive Gabriel
the Second!
Great.
You don't think those names
are too much of a mouthful?
[Gabby grunts]
-[Gabriel growls]
-[HAMURA] Sorry, sorry, sorry...
Well?
The apology did seem legit.
And he gave you guys
a couple of cute names.
Would you like
to go back to him?
[both grunting]
[ASA] That's a no.
[Hamura groans]
They know it takes
more than a night
for someone's mind to change.
It's fine. I can take care
of them for now.
Get back to work.
[Hamura groans]
Break isn't giving you
any trouble
keeping around your new friends?
Nah. Haven't heard
a single peep out of that one.
I guess we're compatible
with Yin and Yang.
Then why not just let 'em
stay contracted to you forever?
The more eyes watchin' over you,
the safer you are.
Hm. You've got a point.
There could still be enemies
lying in wait
right under our noses.
[WOMAN ON SPEAKERS]
That was too close for comfort.
[HAGURE] Yeah.
I panicked when
things didn't go to plan.
Sorry for the trouble
that caused you, Nakagami.
I'll do better next time.
[NAKAGAMI]
About next time...
Should we try hiring
more people?
If you're fine with part-timers,
I've got quite a few.
They're ready to go right now.
[HAGURE] No. I don't need
more warm bodies.
Gabby and Asa have potential.
I believe I can make
good use of them.
[NAKAGAMI]
You'll be okay without backup?
Yes. Or I'll figure it out.
But seriously,
I thought for sure I was gonna
miss my deadline this time!
Whoo, boy.
I have never been so scared!
All my assistants got sick
at the same time!
Then when my files
got corrupted,
I was so behind schedule,
I panicked!
Yeah, that was almost
a total disaster.
And getting the printer
last minute? I had to beg!
I am so sorry for the trouble.
I'll manage my schedule
better next time.
But I really am fine
without more assistants.
Gabby and Asa
have been a great help.
They've been putting
the finishing touches
on my pages!
Aw! You always talk about
how proud you are
of those girls.
They're such sweet kids.
You better be paying them
for all that work.
Well, of course I am!
[NAKAGAMI] Also,
what's going on over there?
Why are all the lights
in your room off?
Are you trying to play the boss
of some evil organization
-or something?
-[Hagure laughs]
[HAGURE] No!
Our house got damaged,
and some parts
still don't have power!
Perfect.
Way easier to move in
than those sandal things.
They're still on us.
[DERA] Not like a simple change
of clothes was gonna shake 'em.
I was considering turning around
to take the initiative.
But sorry. I took your billhook.
Then I completely forgot it
back at Kagemori manor.
If you start swinging that thing
around in a crowded city,
we'll be in trouble,
so you're all good!
Don't sweat it, kid!
Though if you want a weapon,
we could stop by my old pad.
I should probably
grab something, too.
[YURU] You mean your home?
Is it nearby?
[DERA] Just a short walk.
You wouldn't prefer
that we do away
with our tails first?
They'll find out where you live.
[DERA]
Oh, they're gonna find out.
I was gonna
ditch the place anyway,
but let's get some more
use out of it.
It's like a maze here.
[DERA] Don't fall behind, kid.
You'll get lost.
Taking another turn.
[DERA] In here.
You can keep your shoes on.
[switch clicks]
[Yuru exclaims]
Have at it.
Take whatever you want.
[Yuru exclaims contentedly]
I sense the presence
of daemons here.
-What?
-I'd hope so.
[MAN 1]
This is Tadera's safehouse?
Let's not engage them.
The job's done.
We can report this
to the higher-ups.
-[DERA] Leaving so soon?
-[all gasp]
You could at least stay for tea.
[all grunt]
[both grunting]
Damn. [pants]
[DERA] Welcome, friend,
to the Tadera clan's Lost House.
Barely a thing separates
this world from ours.
Unfortunately,
I'm the only one who knows
the route in and out.
So for a first-time visitor
like you,
there's no hope for escape.
Make even one mistake through
the crazy twists and turns,
and you'll be running in circles
till you fall over dead.
[man grunts]
[MAN] Huh? [screams]
[DERA] That's a Kagemori agent
who tailed me once.
You should never follow
a Tadera.
This guy found out why,
as you can see.
There are more like him
scattered around.
You don't wanna
wind up like them,
I suggest you
start talkin' real quick.
[grunts] Damn it.
Oi, Dera!
I still sense the presence
of daemons about here!
I'm well aware. Look.
Those are my family's daemons.
-[MAN] What?
-[YURU] The house?
This pair can come together
to create a Lost House.
-[both gasp]
-[DERA] It's like Higashi.
-Once you enter--
-[RIGHT] No.
Huh?
Not those.
We sense another pair.
[man grunts]
[laughing]
[daemon 2 laughing]
[DAEMON 1] Ooh, lookie!
Oh me, oh my, oh me, oh my!
[DAEMON 2] Been a long while,
Left and Right.
[LEFT] Yuru, Dera,
take this one and fall back.
[both chuckling]
[RIGHT] Tenaga-Ashinaga,
Long-Arm and Long-Leg.
You're no match
for the likes of them.
[both laughing]
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[Long-Leg yells]
[Long-Arm laughs]
[LONG-ARM AND LONG-LEG]
Damn you all!